Bear’s Baumkuchen Shop
Children, you didn’t forget anything, did you?
You brought your lunches, drinking water and treats with you?
Yes!
Fujimoto-kun, Kobato-chan, you two didn’t forget anything either, right?
You’re not bringing anything on the field trip?
I’m sorry. I’ll go get my bag!
Kobato-chan, are you all right?
I’m all right.
Oh, it’s just you, Kobato.
Ioryogi-san, let’s go!
What?
Everyone’s going on a field trip.
Ah, so that’s why you seemed so happy today.
Yes! It seems like it’ll be really fun.
That’s why you should come as well.
I wonder.
Um... Uh...
What are you doing? You have to answer it!
Y-Yes!
Hello! Hanato Kobato!
Kobato…?
Ah! I messed up! It's Yomogi Preschool!
Who are you?
I’m helping out here.
You’re lively.
Thank you very much.
Where’s Sayaka? I’d like to speak with her.
Um, she‘s just about to go on a field trip.
Do you have some sort of business with her?
Yes, I do. Could you give her a message for me?
Yes!
She needs to close down the
school and leave immediately.
Eh?
Her loan will not be extended any further.
Are you the debt collector?
Earlier, they came to the
preschool and bullied everyone.
They did that?
I-I’m sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
Because you didn’t do it, so I thought you might get upset.
What a funny girl!
What?
Regrettably, your help there is no longer needed.
Eh?
I’m going to crush the preschool.
Huh?
That’s…
Please pass the message on to Sayaka.
U-Um, who are…
Crush the preschool?
I wonder if that person was an
acquaintance of Sayaka-sensei?
I’m passing on the field trip.
Ioryogi-san?
I’ll be taking a nap until you get back.
Geez, you’re late.
How long were you going to make us wait?
Thanks to you, we're already late.
I was just wondering if the debt collector is an acquaintance of Sayaka-sensei.
What?
Just now, a man called.
He said he was going to crush the preschool.
It’s him.
Don’t tell Sayaka-sensei about the phone call.
But he seemed like such a scary person.
It’s okay, just stay quiet.
Kobato-chan, Fujimoto-kun, we’re leaving.
I’m sorry! We’re coming.
Like always, the entrance was left in a strange spot.
Welcome!
Hey.
Oh, it’s you.
Did you have to insert yourself in the shop’s name?
It can’t be helped.
On top of having to work here, the shop was also named after me.
That character decided that too?
Don’t say “that character.”
You’re still not disgusted with what you turned into?
There’s nothing to be disgusted with! I’m fine the way I am!
Why did you have to rage like that?! And yet you complain, you idiot!
If they heard that kind of talk from you, you wouldn't even be a stuffed animal next time.
You’d be the size of a finger puppet!
Now that that’s over, what did you come here for today?
Ah…
What is it? Get over your pride.
There’s something I’d like you to look into for me.
Sit. I guess I’ll listen to you after all.
Ooooh!
So tall!
Look over there!
What?
A lake, a huge lake.
I’m going to crush the school.
I wonder who the person on the phone was.
Kobato-chan.
Toshihiko-kun, Marina-chan,
we’re going to eat lunch soon.
Okay!
Mr. Bump appeared on my head!
Kobato-chan, you’ve been doing painful things since this morning.
You‘re pretty spaced out.
Is something bothering you, Kobato-chan?
Um…
Isn’t she always spaced out?
Not always!
Don’t give Sayaka-sensei extra things to worry about.
Yes...
So, you want information about the people involved with Yomogi Preschool?
Yeah.
What now? Has that pitiful form left your data gathering abilities rusty?
My form aside, yours is a million times more pitiful.
But anyway, to hear you ask something like that…
Huh?
Long ago, the only thing you’d say is “research it!”
If I didn’t listen to you, along came the firebreathing and the fists.
Then to fulfill your expectations, I’ll give you an extra large helping!
Stop it!
Ah, they’re finished.
Hey, haven’t you become a little too used to this job?!
If your former subordinates saw the way you are now, they'd probably cry.
I don’t want to hear that from a stuffed animal like you.
What are you saying?
I’ll take on that job you talked about earlier.
It has something to do with that young lady, right?
Yeah, thanks.
This time, I’ll do it as a favor to you.
Delicious!
Why are you eating at your own leisure?!
Kobato-chan.
Marina-chan, what’s wrong?
Kobato-chan, are you worried about something?
Huh? Um, uh…
Nothing at all! That’s the truth!
There is something.
It’s okay. I know something good.
Huh?
When you find it, you’ll be happy.
Kobato-chan, Marina, we’re going to play hide-and-seek.
Yes!
I’m coming!
Rock, paper, scissors!
One more time.
Kobato-chan is it!
While Kobato-chan is counting to 10, everyone hide.
Look for us, all right?
Okay! I’m going to do my best!
This is all I got for a souvenir? Really.
Stack them as high as you want, I can carry anything!
This form is such a pain!
It’s also quite pathetic.
I don’t want to hear that from you.
It’s been a while, hasn’t it, Ginsei?
That really is a shameful form.
What are you saying?
The appearance may have changed, but inside you’re still the same.
Aren’t you coming back to the spirit world?
There are things I have to do.
That little girl?
If you put a hand on Kobato, I’ll strangle you.
Don’t forget…
We will settle this once and for all!
What a pain!
Where is everyone hiding?
Not here.
Everyone, where are you?
Kobato-chan looks like she’s having fun.
Kobato-chan still hasn’t found anyone.
She’s starting to look in another strange place.
Looks like this is going to take a while.
Everyone’s so good at hiding.
Hey!
Fujimoto-san?
We’re going home soon.
We can’t! Right now, I’m it!
Huh?
“It” has to find the people who are hiding.
But it’s time…
Kids, we’re leaving!
Okay!
There you are!
Kobato-chan, are you all right?
Toshihiko-kun and Yoshio-kun, I found you!
She did!
We were found!
Yuzuru-kun, Yukari-chan, I found you!
Ah, Masao-kun too!
You’re there as well.
And you’re over there too.
There too!
Kobato-chan, you have a leaf stuck in your hair again.
You’re so clumsy. Get it for her.
Thank you very much!
Well, let’s go.
Okay.
Lastly, let’s take a keepsake picture together.
Huh? Where’s Marina-chan?
She’s not here.
I’ll go look.
Fujimoto-kun.
Sayaka-sensei, please stay here with the kids.
I’ll go look too.
Marina-chan!
Marina!
Find her?
No.
I wonder if she’s hiding somewhere.
I hope that’s the case.
If only I could have found them faster.
Let’s try looking over there.
Marina!
Marina-chan!
Marina-chan?!
She’s sleeping.
Thank goodness!
Marina-chan.
Good morning.
Kobato-chan?
Sorry, when I couldn’t find any…
For hide-and-seek?
No, the four-leaf clover.
If you find it, you’ll be happy.
I thought I’d give it to you.
To me?
Yeah, you were so sad today.
I looked everywhere but there weren’t any.
I’m sorry.
It’s okay that you didn’t find it.
I’m happy.
It cheers me up that you tried to find me some happiness.
That’s great!
This is a nice place, so let’s take the picture here.
Okay, nobody move.
Kiyokazu-sensei, hurry!
It’s fine, just look forward.
What is it?
There it is!
The four-leaf clover.
Here you go.
Thank you, Kobato-chan!
Kobato-chan, look!
Look!
There are so many of them!
There’re lots and lots. It looks like we found happiness.
Hey, we’re taking another picture!
Okay!
The baumkuchen is all tattered.
And it was from Genko-sama too!
It’s just one thing after another! What is it now?
You work for that old bear back there. That would make you…
Nope, I forgot.
That hurt! It’s Zuishou!
I have a message from Genko-sama!
He’s done looking into your request!
What?
As expected.
So, you can laugh nihilistically, looking like that?
What? You damn bird!
I’m back!
Huh?
Ioryogi-san isn’t back yet.
Ioryogi-san is small, so what if he’s stuck somewhere,
or fell in a hole in the road,
or someone sat on him?
Oh, this is terrible. He’s in big trouble!
Who’s in trouble?
Ioryogi-san!
Yeah?
Welcome back!
What’s that?
Yeah, this thing?
It’s a baumkuchen.
So? How was the field trip?
I have something for you.
Here.
It’s a Happiness Clover, but it’s wilted a little.
It’s so you can find happiness too.
I want everyone at Yomogi
Preschool to always be happy.
I’m to inform you that the previous head of Yomogi Preschool,
appears to have been tricked into taking out a loan.
The previous head?
Yes, Okiura Sayaka’s father, but he died two years ago.
The trickster is a pretty dangerous fellow, and it involves a close relative of Okiura Sayaka.
Now that’s a problem.
At this rate, sooner or later, Yomogi Preschool will be crushed.